{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Land Surveyors","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"__cache./api/resource/task/40156/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40156,"taskName":"Land Surveyor","taskDescription":"Survey Property","xmTaskDescriptor":"Land Surveyors","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":142,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Architect architects engineer evaluate survey","textMessagingName":"Land Surveyor","rolloverLongDesc":"Surveyors work from official land records \u0026 clues on the site to establish the exact size of a property as well as the exact location of boundaries with other properties. Often used when property is sold or when fences \u0026 walls are being planned.","rolloverShortDesc":"Establish exact size \u0026 location of boundaries.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Survey Property.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Land Surveyor | \u003ccity\u003e Property Survey | Survey Land","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":5,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Land Surveyor","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Land Surveyor","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Land Surveyor Need","urlName":"Land-Surveyor","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Land Surveyors \u003cin_city\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Property Survey","searchKeywords":"Architect,architects,engineer,evaluate,survey,surveyors,local,surveying,inspector,evaluator,inspect,hiring,hire,engineering,architecture,Surveyor,Land","emcCategoryOid":-12005,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":466,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40156/":{"taskOID":40156,"originalTaskOID":40156,"setID":466,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1525,"questionDisplayText":"Survey Purpose","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the description of this survey.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1093,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Boundary survey (American Land Title Association)","answerDisplayText":"Boundary survey (American Land Title Association)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6434,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Topographic or site map survey","answerDisplayText":"Topographic or site map survey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4737,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Plot survey (subdivision/boundary alteration plots)","answerDisplayText":"Plot survey (subdivision/boundary alteration plots)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1600,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Construction survey","answerDisplayText":"Construction survey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2200,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Elevation certification (e.g. for flood insurance)","answerDisplayText":"Elevation certification (e.g. for flood insurance)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1525,"questionDisplayText":"Survey Purpose","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Select the description of this survey.","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1093,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Boundary survey (American Land Title Association)","answerDisplayText":"Boundary survey (American Land Title Association)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6434,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Topographic or site map survey","answerDisplayText":"Topographic or site map survey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4737,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Plot survey (subdivision/boundary alteration plots)","answerDisplayText":"Plot survey (subdivision/boundary alteration plots)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1600,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Construction survey","answerDisplayText":"Construction survey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2200,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Elevation certification (e.g. for flood insurance)","answerDisplayText":"Elevation certification (e.g. for flood insurance)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1093,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Boundary survey (American Land Title Association)","answerDisplayText":"Boundary survey (American Land Title Association)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6434,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Topographic or site map survey","answerDisplayText":"Topographic or site map survey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4737,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Plot survey (subdivision/boundary alteration plots)","answerDisplayText":"Plot survey (subdivision/boundary alteration plots)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1600,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Construction survey","answerDisplayText":"Construction survey","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2200,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Elevation certification (e.g. for flood insurance)","answerDisplayText":"Elevation certification (e.g. for flood insurance)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]}}